What a waste, though...
To think that you actually rejected Madoka-chan!
It doesn't matter whether I accepted or rejected her.
I've already told you, time and time again, there's nothing between us!
You've been bugging me non-stop about this ever since school started, too.
That's because it's Madoka-chan!
That...
...poyoyon, poyoyon, purururunru-
Good morning!
Good morning...
Good morning, Madoka-chan.
futari de mita haruka kanata no ryuusei
二人で見た遥か彼方の流星
The distant shooting star we saw.
haato no puromisu
ハートのプロミス
Believe in our promise. As much as you'd call it true love.
ai to ieru hodo shinjite
愛と言えるほど信じて
You stop, as if you'd do that...
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
Chihiro Fansubs Presents
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
kaze ni yureru kami osaeru you ni
風に揺れる髪　抑えるように
...to keep your hair from fluttering in the wind.
kimi wa tomadoi
君は戸惑い
I painted my cheeks red...
koi no hajimari to kidukanai de hoo wo akakushita
恋の始まりと気づかないで 頬を赤くした
...so I wouldn't notice that I had fallen in love.
ikusen no hikari ryoute de hora
幾千の光両手でほら
You have myriads of light rays in your hand.
hoshi wo sukutte
星をすくって
Come on and save that star.
hitori no yoru demo waraeru you ni
一人の夜でも　笑えるように
So you can smile even on a night when you're alone.
omoi de wo hanabi ni shite
想い出の花火にして
Turn them into fireworks of your memories.
kimi to boku no uta ni nare
君と僕の唄になれ
And let them become a song for us.
saa ten made todoke kono kimochi
さぁ天まで届けこの気持ち
Let the heavens know...
kokoro wo gyutto tsunagou
心をぎゅっト繋ごう
...about our love that connects us firmly.
yowakutatte iin da boku no te de
弱くたっていいんだ僕の手で
It's okay if you're weak.
sono yume wo hippatte iku
その夢をひっぱっていく
I'll grab your hand and realise your dream.
kakehashi ni na itai yo
架け橋になりたいよ
I want to become your only bridge.
kimi hitori no kirari niji ni naru deshou
君一人のキラリ虹になるでしょう
I'm sure we will be shining forever...
boku ni kimi wo eien ni
僕に君を永遠に
...brightly like a rainbow.
Episode 11
When the Rain Falls
So they chose Tsumugi-san to play the role of Megami for this years festival.
Yup!
Hina-senpai and I are going to play the role of the Arks.
Ah, the ones holding the scrolls for the Megami, right?
But, wouldn't it be better to choose the Megami with a vote?
Eh?
The Ogami's role is played by Hoshino this year, right?
Wouldn't it be a good chance to confess bravely to him during the ceremony?
Eh?!
What are you talking about, Ibuki-chan?!
Sure, I've heard stories about people confessing during the ceremony,
but they all happened long ago, and the one who confessed was the Ogami-
These days, men and women are equal.
It'd be fine, even if the Megami confessed, wouldn't it?
Ah, I see.
That's not the point!
Kazu-kun is more of a...
How should I put it...?
Like an older brother...
Confessing would be a little...
If you keep telling yourself that, someone else might steal him.
What do you mean by "another girl"...?
For example, Hina-senpai, or maybe Koyori-chan...
That's impossible!
...or maybe...
...me.
Eh?
I was just joking!
Oh, it was just a joke.
Gosh, don't scare me like that!
Hinata
"Just a joke", huh?
A confession?
It's just so sudden.
I don't know what to do.
What if I really did confess to him and he said "Okay"?
And, then...
And, then... maybe...!
Ah, yes. Have to pick it up.
Hello?
Ah, Ayumu-kun?
Eh?!
You want me... to be your model?!
You sure slept in, didn't you?
Ah, good morning.
It's already afternoon, you know.
Even if it's Sunday, aren't you taking it a bit too easy?
Sorry about that.
I stayed up late yesterday-
Huh?
What's wrong?
Ah, nothing.
It feels like déjà vu...
I feel like this has happened before.
Does the déjà vu matter?
It's been like this every Sunday since you got here.
Now, please eat your food and go out for a walk or something.
I'm going to clean your room, and it'll be a pain if you're around.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Well then, I'll be off.
Have a good time.
Take your time on your stroll, okay?
Ayumu-kun!
She says stroll, but...
I have no choice but to go back to the shrine again.
No, maybe I should pay a visit to the shopping district.
Oh, Ibuki?
Ah!
H-Hoshino...
What are you doing here?
I'm not doing anything.
It's just...
I had some time off.
So, the same as me, then.
You want some?
I don't.
I don't want an indirect kiss with you.
Don't you usually go out with Ui when you're free?
I do.
All the time.
But she said she had plans today.
I see.
And, she's alone with him right now, and she might say something weird.
I know!
Hey, let's go to Honchou and play!
Wait, just the two of us?
When I couldn't go because I had club activities,
you guys went to Honchou and had fun, right?
Ah, yeah...
This is the time to compensate!
Hmm...
Okay!
Let's go and take revenge for you, then!
Yup!
Excuse me...
I'm sorry to have you come on a Sunday.
It's fine!
I didn't have anything planned, anyway.
I'll be taking out my equipment now.
Then, I'll...
W-Why are you taking off your clothes?
Eh?!
Ah, I'm sorry!
When I heard that I was going to be a model for your picture,
I assumed it was going to be a nude one...
That's not what I wanted!
Sky
sumiwataru
It's clear and blue
sora no shita
I'm under the sky
kono machi no naka
in the middle of this city
Heart
kono mune ni
It's in my chest,
furi tsumoru
filling up
yasashii memory
with tender memories
Oh baby kyuuni no egao
Oh baby, your sudden smile
kitto mini yakitsukete
will light up the night sky
Baby isshun datte
Baby, I won't let a moment
minogase nai kara
slip past me
Shining shining sky
konna jikan ga
If only these times
Oh shining shining smile
tsudzukeba ii na
could last forever
Shining Shining Days
hoshizora no shita
under the starry sky
Wishing your star
Wishing my star
tsutaete yo
Convey it
It's my message
All that singing made me thirsty.
Yes?
Sorry to disturb you.
Wow!
This is their famous Honey Toast!
Huh?
Did we ask for this?
Today is Couple's Day, so we're doing a special service.
Couple?!
To preserve this memory, we will take a photo of you drinking this together.
Will that be all right?
Ui-san, let's take a break.
Yup!
Oyake really are the best in autumn!
You must be tired from sitting still the whole time.
I'm sorry.
I'm not tired, but my shoulders are a bit stiff.
I should have told you earlier, but when I'm done with this picture,
I want to give it to Onii-chan as a present!
Eh?!
To Kazu-kun?
You don't want me to?
Ah, I'm fine with it, but why?
During summer vacation, when we went to the beach, Tsumugi-san told me this:
That's wrong, Ayumu-kun.
Kazuma-san has been working so hard for you in order to let you smile.
However, if you make such a sad face because of that,
Kazuma-san would definitely be disheartened.
If you're grateful to Kazuma-san,
instead of thinking about how you've been causing him trouble,
try smiling for his efforts in order to make him smile.
Wouldn't that be good?
That's why I was thinking about what I could do to make Onii-chan smile.
Then, I remembered that when I was small,
I gave Onii-chan a picture and he was really happy with it.
So...
"Thinking about what I could do to make Onii-chan smile"...
But, why did you choose me to be your model?
Well, isn't Ui-san dating Onii-chan?
Eh?!
That's why I thought that Onii-chan would be happiest with a picture of the girl he likes.
Was I wrong?
Kasane-chan said that the reason why Onii-chan didn't want to date Madoka-san...
...was because he was already dating you.
So, I assumed...
That's not true!
I'm not dating Kazu-kun yet-
Actually, Kazu-kun is like a brother to me...
That's not right.
Tsumugi-san!
Kazuma-san is Ayumu-kun's brother.
Not Ui-chan's.
Oh, this is very well-drawn!
When it's done, Kazuma-san will definitely be very happy.
Good luck with the rest!
Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi
Thank you very much for today.
And, please keep this a secret from Onii-chan.
Yup, I will...
Well, it's just if...
If I really dated Kazu-kun, would you be fine with it?
Well, if I dated Kazu-kun, I would be taking your brother away from you.
Even so...
Even so, Ayumu-kun, are you fine with that?
That's true...
If that happened, I might become lonely.
But, if that makes Onii-chan smile, I'll be happy, too!
Ah, that was fun!
Looks like we managed to get your revenge, huh?
Yup!
Ah, just when I was wondering what you were drinking...
Did you really want to drink that cream soda with me back then?
Idiot! That's not true!
Do you think we really looked like a couple?
So... Do you want to keep going, and date me for real?
Eh?
What are you talking about?
Keep the jokes to a limit.
That's true!
Sorry for saying something weird.
Just kidding!
Just kidding...
Do you think we really looked like a couple?
Do you want to keep going, and date me for real?
That's true!
Sorry for saying something weird.
Ibuki!
Sorry!
Well... It's...
I think I misunderstood you. It's really embarrassing!
When you asked if we should date...
If...
If you were being serious, I'm really sorry!
It was really sudden, so I didn't know
what to say, and it turned out like that...
You're an idiot.
That was...
That was obviously a joke.
Yet you still came running back like that.
That's so stupid.
That was...
That couldn't have been true.
I'm back.
Welcome home!
My, you're soaking wet.
Yeah.
I got rejected.
Nakatsugawa
"Thinking about what I could do to make Onii-chan smile", huh?
Even though I like my brother,
I never tried to make him happy.
On top of that, I gave him and his wife Kuriko-san a sad face.
Why didn't I say "Congratulations" on that day...?
If I had congratulated them properly,
Onii-chan would definitely have been happy.
That's it!
Even though it's very late, and it might not make him happy,
I'll call Onii-chan!
And I'll give him the "Congratulations!" I couldn't say that day!
Onii-chan
Ah, Onii-chan, it's me!
Oh, what a coincidence.
I was just about to give you a call-
Listen, Onii-chan!
Well, I...
I have something to tell you, Onii-chan.
It might seem a bit sudden, but... I just have to tell you.
So, well... well...
Anyway, congratulations!
What a shock.
How did you know?
Kuriko had a baby.
I found out when I went to the hospital,
and when I was just about to call you, you called me.
Hey, Ui.
Will you repeat what you just said to Kuriko, too?
Ah...
Yup!
Hinata
My, you're up early.
Do you have morning practice at the Archery Club?
That's not it.
I have something to take care of.
I see.
Have you eaten your breakfast?
Then, I'll be off!
Hoshino Kazuma, you idiot!
You're the worst person around here!
Okay!
Ibuki-chan! Ibuki-chan!
Ui, what's wr-
Listen!
Listen, listen!
There's a baby on the way!
Eh?!
And now I'm an aunt!
Hold on, calm down a bit!
I'm telling you, Onii-chan had a baby!
Oh, the one that gave birth isn't Onii-chan, but his wife.
I know that.
Wait, so you're an aunt...!
Yup!
chotto matte yo
ちょっと待ってよ
Wait a second!
yume no tsuzuki kana
夢の続きかな
Why are you continuing with your daydreams!
shigyou beru no gofun mae da (u—n)
始業ベルの五分前だ(うーん)
You were studying just five minutes ago
mezamashi mo nidone
目覚ましも二度寝
Your alarm clock already rang twice
ja shouganai ne
じゃ、しょうがないね
So it can't be helped
yada seifuku no manma nechattetanda demo rakkii
やだっ制服のまんま寝ちゃってたんだ... でもラッキー?
Oh no! I slept with my uniform on, but how lucky!
hai tenshon de ikou konna tokya!
ハイテンションでいこう こんな時ゃ!
It's time to go with high tension!
nandemo kandemo DORAMA ja arumaishi
何でもかんでもドラマじゃあるまいし
Everything isn't like in drama's
umakuiku monka tte omotteta (fu—n)
うまくいくもんかって思ってた(ふーん)
I thought it would turn out smoothly
shokupan wo kajiri
食パンをかじり
Nibbling on white bread
kado wo magaru
角を曲がる
Make the corner curve
to hatto! masaka ne
とハッと...! まさかね
See! It's impossible!
sukippu sukippu
スキップスキップ
Skip! Skip!
mousou darake de
妄想だらけで
Full of crazy ideas!
dasshu dasshu
ダッシュダッシュ
Dash! Dash!
chikoku wa genjitsu sokka sokka
遅刻は現実 そっかそっか
Being late has become reality, I see, I see
sekai wa kyou mo todokoori naku janjan mawaruyo
世界は今日も 滞りなくじゃんじゃんまわるよ
The world today is also filled with love, climbing non-stop
ii kanji de (hai)
いい感じで(ハイ)
It feels great
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! or GO!
Go or Go
itsudatte
いつだって
As always,
kyou ga numbah one saikou tte sakende ikiteyaru
今日がNo.1 最高って叫んで生きてやる
Shout out, "Today is number one!" "Today's the best!"
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! & GO!
Go & Go
tatoeba hito tobi taimumashin de
例えばひとッ飛びタイムマシーンで
For example, a one-leap time machine.
sore tte saikou (saiko desu—)
それって最高(さいこですー)
That's the greatest!
Next time, on Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi, the final episode:
The Starry Bridge that Leads to the Night Sky.
Episode 12
The Starry Bridge that Leads to the Night Sky
So, we've finally reached the end.
Thinking back, a lot of things have happened.
Things like "It tasted like cheese", "If you insert an acorn it hurts".
Also "Pink Nyanbobo", "Onii-chan's King Cobra is chasing after me",
"Since this isn't panties but a Fundoshi, I'm not embarrassed".
I had doubts about impure love, but in the end, it has to end like this!
Loving your little brother is just!
No matter what you write it with, it's just!